honeyfeed.fm 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy | Honeyfeed

Your privacy is important for us at Honeyfeed.fm. We designed our Privacy Policy to cover how we collect, use and share your information, so please take a moment to learn about our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@honeyfeed.fm

## Acceptance of the Privacy Policy

The Terms of Service of Honeyfeed.fm are incorporated herein by reference. By using the service, you agree to be bound by the Terms of Service. The term “we”, “us”, or “our” means qdopp, Inc. and our affiliates and subsidiaries.

## Collection of information and use by Honeyfeed

People have different personal privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.

We collect personal information when you register with Honeyfeed.fm. Honeyfeed.fm may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies such as Google, for the purpose of delivering personalized content. When you register, we ask for information such as your name and email address. Honeyfeed.fm uses the information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research.

* Information you provide

We collect information you provide when you create a Honeyfeed account, upload User Submissions, or otherwise use the service, including:

Identification information. For example, your email address, username, and authentication credentials used to sign up or log in. If you choose to add a photo, location, or other optional details to your profile, you should be aware that such information is public, and therefore visible to anyone who visits your profile page.

* Information we collect from your use of the service

We collect information about you and the devices you use to access the Service, such as your computer, mobile phone, or tablet.

* The information that we collect includes:

Device information. We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, [unique device identifiers](https://policies.google.com/privacy/key-terms?hl=en#toc-terms-unique-device-id)

, and mobile network information including phone number). Honeyfeed may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Honeyfeed user account.

Log information. When you use our services or view Content provided on the service, we may automatically collect and store certain information in [server logs](https://policies.google.com/privacy/key-terms?hl=en#toc-terms-server-logs) . This may include:

Details of how you used our service, such as your search queries, reading history, bookmarks, and transaction history;

[Internet protocol (IP) address](https://policies.google.com/privacy/key-terms?hl=en#toc-terms-ip) ;

Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL;

Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Honeyfeed user account.

Some data is necessary for enabling us to provide the registration to and usage of our services. This includes the data below.

Item| Types of Data| Purpose of use  
---|---|---  
Basic information| 

  * E-mail address

| To help us develop, deliver, and improve our Services, including the following aspects of our Services:

  * Messaging and other communication to and with users
  * The creation, updating, accessing, and maintaining of "My Library"
  * social communication and user-interactive features
  * providing end-user support.

Data about your account and use of services| 

  * Log-in ID
  * Password
  * User ID

Data we collect with Cookies| 

  * Session ID
  * Browser ID

Information from Third Parties| 

  * Facebook user ID
  * Twitter user ID
  * Google user ID

IP address| 

  * IP address

| To prevent and take measures against fraud, illegal activities, infringement of our rights or interests, or breaches of our Terms of Service, and this Privacy Policy.  
Data about your account and use of services| 

  * Log-in ID
  * Password
  * User ID

Basic Information| 

  * E-mail address

| To send important notices, such as changes to our Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, or other services-specific policies.  
  
To send important notices, such as changes to our Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, or other services-specific policies.

How long we retain your information

We retain data until it is no longer necessary to provide our services to you, or until your account is deleted - whichever comes first. If you no longer want Honeyfeed to use your information to provide the services to you, you maydelete your account from the edit profile menu.

## Policy not to collect personal information from children

Honeyfeed does not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the service is directed to or intended for children under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, you may alert us via the email address at the bottom of this page. If we learn that we have collected any personal information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child's account.

## Information sharing

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

## Cookies and other tracking technologies

As discussed below, some information is collected about you automatically through cookies and other tracking technologies.

We use “cookies” on Honeyfeed.fm to track how users use our website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We link some information we store in cookies to personal information you submit in order to deliver a better experience on the service.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. These are non-personal information which includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, may be limited.

You can change your browser settings to reject all cookies, accept only certain cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Please note that you may need to renew these settings if you delete your cookies after these preferences are made. These settings also may not apply if you are using a different computer or Internet browser. To opt out of having information collected by third party ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers used for behavioral advertising, to obtain information about the technologies these third parties might use, and to view information regarding their Privacy Policies, please visit: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> if you are located in the United States, <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/> if you are located in Europe, <http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices> if you are located in Canada, or [http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au](http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au/) if you are located in Australia.

If you opt out of these technologies, you will continue to see advertising displayed on the site, but the advertising may not be targeted to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over, advertisers' or service providers' cookies, and the information practices of third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. For more information on the use of cookies in online advertising, please visit the [NAI's website](http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au/).

## Behavioral targeting / Re-targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Please note this does not opt you out of being served to advertise. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Content of items

The contents of any item that you post directly to the site, including any text, images, and audio, are stored and maintained on our servers in order to publish these items and provide the service. Your User Submitted Content will be associated with your account.

## Confidentiality and security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution if they fail to meet these obligations. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is secure, however, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Third party sites

This Policy only applies to the Honeyfeed.fm website and services. We do not exercise control over the sites that our service links to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We encourage you to read such Privacy Policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personal information, and we shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personal information by any third party.

We partner with third parties to manage our advertising. Our third-party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising visit <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/> (or if you're located in the European Union, visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/> ). Please note you might continue to receive generic ads.

Third-party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information about user visits in order to provide advertisements for goods and services that may be of interest to the user.

## Data integrity

We process personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. Users can update, correct or delete their personal information through the profile page of their account or by contacting us.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Withdrawing consent

You have the right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your information and your use of our services. For example:

You can choose to withdraw your consent to our processing of your data and your use of the services by closing your account, by using the "Delete your account" option in your Honeyfeed edit profile settings.This link can be useful to delete your account from the edit profile menu.

Depending on your location, you can also email info@honeyfeed.fm to request that your personal information be deleted, excluding information we are legally required to retain.

## Social media widgets

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook and Twitter button and widgets, such as the "share this" button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the company providing it.

## Single sign-on

You may log in to our website using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Social Plug-ins and Public Spaces

Your information may also be made available to us when you register with any SNS for use of our services and/or permit any SNS to share any of your information with us in connection with your use of our services, including any profile information (such as username, images, date of birth, real name), type of Device, SNS account ID, gender, location information, and your SNS friends' lists, and when any changes are made to that information. By accepting an SNS's applicable terms, you agree and consent to the SNS making such information available to us on those terms.

  * Twitter  
\- Website: <https://twitter.com/>  
\- Privacy Policy: <https://twitter.com/privacy>
  * Facebook  
\- Website: <https://www.facebook.com/>  
\- Privacy Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update>
  * Google+  
\- Website: <https://plus.google.com/about>  
\- Privacy Policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

Be aware that any personal information that you choose to share in public spaces such as comments or profile walls can be read, collected, or used by others, or could be used to send unsolicited messages to you. Honeyfeed generally does not remove Content from public spaces, so some of your posts or comments may remain public even after your account is deleted, though your name and profile icon will no longer be displayed alongside any posts. You are responsible for the personal information that you choose to post in public spaces through the services.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Honeyfeed.fm account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our Privacy Practices. Your use of our services after we have changed the Privacy Policy will indicate your consent to the updated Privacy Policy.

## Visitors from outside Japan

The site's offices are located in Japan. If you visit the site from another country, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of she Site may be processed in and transferred to Japan and will be subject to Japan law. Japan’s privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence. By using the site or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in Japan.

## Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).  
If you no longer wish to use the Services or receive service-related communications (except for legally required notices), then you may delete your account.You can delete your account from the edit profile menu.

## Contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through the email below:

Contact email: info@honeyfeed.fm

## Latest update

August 17, 2018
